sustainablelifemedia.com 2008-09-26

# Our Privacy Policy | Sustainable Life Media

Sustainable Life Media (SLM) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to its website (the Site). 

  The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit the Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to manage and edit, the information. This Privacy Policy applies to the Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites to which we link. 

  **Information Collection**

  We collect personal information when you wish to use certain features of the Site, such as creating a profile, joining one of our mailing lists, registering for SLM events, or sending feedback to us. When you choose to use these features, we ask for information such as your name, email address, mailing address, and other demographic and personal information. We use the information that you provide for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain services offered through the Site. 

  Through the Site, we may automatically gather certain information about the use of the Site, such as how frequently certain areas of the Site are visited including through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other technologies. 

  **Disclosure**

  We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may permit certain trusted partners to access your information in connection with their performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. We do not otherwise disclose any personal information that you provide to us or any information about your individual visits to our site except when we believe in good faith (i) that the law requires such disclosure or (ii) that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights and property of SLM or others. 

  We use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate, so that we can improve the Site and for business and administrative purposes. We also may use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information. 

  **Updating Personal Information and Preferences**

  If you have signed up for one of our mailing lists and would like to update your contact information or cancel your subscription, you may do so by going to the SLM website and clicking My Profile. You also may cancel your subscription by clicking on the unsubscribe link in emails that you receive from SLM or by replying to such email and placing the word unsubscribe in the subject line. 

   **Privacy Policy Changes**

  If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for the Site, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

  If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please [contact us](mailto:info@sustainablelifemedia.com).
